Hello. - Hello.
Just a fringe here.
Just the bangs.
You know...
Room Ello did it, didn't she?
Yeah, it's long. Yeah, it grew long.
The moment she did this, the battery died.
The cordless one...
The cordless one.
So we're the only ones who didn't lose?
So we only lost here? Only here.
That was close.
Braids are cute.
Braids, mom.
They're so cute!
Superb angle! It can't be helped.
I forgive you. What's with the puzzle symbols?
What's that?
What's that? Quiz adventure time!
What's the point of this if you're going to cut me off?
What's that? What's that?
What's the point of hanging up on me?
So many things happened!
So many things happened...
I made a mistake.
Never mind.
Yes, I was talking about your job.
Yes, our job.
Mm-hmm.
Miss...
Who's that?
Terada's Mesan.
Ah.
Long time no see.
Last time we stayed at Yuno's house.
That's right.
We had a sleepover together.
How was it?
It was fun. We sang an exclusive song together.
Hey, just so you know.
I was looking at the lyrics to "Exclusive and Seductive.
The lyrics?
Yeah.
It was fun.
Nice. Sounds fun.
Did you hear Yuno was the MC at "What's Up?" last night?
I haven't heard it yet. I'm going to listen to it now.
I listen to it every week.
I'll listen to it.
I'm kind of looking forward to Yuno's MC.
I thought it was going to be Mire.
I didn't expect it to be Yuno.
I thought it was Mire too, so I was relieved.
I got a line from Yuno, and it was Yuno!
What a surprise!
I wonder how it went.
I'm looking forward to it.
When I talked about Mei's exclusivity...
Laugh, laugh, laugh, laugh, laugh.
Let's laugh.
Yeah, it was funny.
Yuno, Yuno's mom and
Mei's sleepover party
Yuno's mom?
Yeah, we'll be together.
That's nice.
Good night.
What did you eat?
With Mei.
You didn't have lunch?
No, we didn't have dinner, but we did go to Kura Sushi for lunch.
Oh, Kura Sushi?
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
So, the Mario game's fun, huh? It's fun.
There's a new Mario Wonder one that just came out, and I started playing it.
What's that? Switch? Switch.
Yeah, it was a lot of fun. It's fun.
It's fun. That's it, right? Isn't that MariCar?
It's like Maricar, right? Yeah, you know, that.
You just click it and it goes flying. Sounds fun.
Yes, it is.
Black sushi... Yu likes tuna.
Is that all you can eat? Yu no.
No, I can eat anything.
It's a mystery.
She only eats marinated tuna.
And sammo?
I can't eat it, but I can eat it if it's grilled.
Oh, that's a tough one.
Yes, it's my birthday today.
Really? Happy birthday.
Don't doubt it.
Happy birthday.
Tuna tofugu, steamed persimmon and grilled salmon. Maybe salmon is baked.
I can eat the basics.
Raw is like that, but if it's grilled, I eat it all the time.
I don't like the idea of eating it all the time.
He likes grilled squid.
He was so happy at the festival.
Festival? Yeah.
He ate two of them.
Yeah. I think it's amazing.
It was on my hand more than I expected.
I'll eat it, I'll eat it, I'll eat it.
I know, I don't like avocados.
Why is that?
He said, "I'm a bit scared of avocados.
I'm so cute, so cute. It's not here now.
They always think I'm a set of "Iro-no-no-kawa".
Why?
What?
I ate some taro kenpis and they know who makes them!
What? Why?
What? You're kidding, right?
Oh, my God.
Where does it say that?
It says...
What? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's the same kanji.
It's true.
That's amazing!
What's going on?
Maybe they're from the same area.
That's amazing.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I know.
You scared the shit out of me. I could tell from this one.
I mean, how often do you find out who your maker is?
He recognized it right away because he loves it. That's amazing. That's amazing.
You're right. It's amazing.
You were right.
Your bangs are amazing.
They're so smooth.
They're so smooth today.
They're long.
I added more bangs.
Oh, they're long.
Oh, it's long.
It's the size of your face.
Bigger than your face?
Yeah, it is.
Can you give me a squash time, please?
Okay.
That's it.
That's good.
Did you get your license?
One moment, please.
You haven't even tried to get it yet.
That's right.
Hold on a second.
Do you know what it's like to want to get a license?
I'm almost there.
Just a minute.
Yes, sir.
You're an amazing guy.
Yeah, it's great.
I've always wanted to ride a bike.
A license would be nice.
Don't ever do that.
No, something else.
If someone wants to get a motorcycle license...
I'd say, "Go for it.
You tell them.
It's dangerous.
You know how I worry?
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, this is cute. This hoodie is cute.
Yeah, it's cute.
I opened it and found Pedro's long T-shirt.
I told you it's not good for a motorcycle. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'll be there.
Thailand has so many bikes that everyone is missing four. Yes, there are a lot of bikes in Thailand.
That's why I wanted to ride. I am easily influenced.
I wanted to go to Pedro. I heard that the ticket price for the 100-yen ticket was very high, so I got it by myself.
I was able to get it by myself.
Both.
It was a little far from the first floor and the second floor, but I was able to see it.
It was amazing.
Ayuni-chan was even cute!
Is this where Ayuni is?
Yes, I know someone named Gino who is in the band that Ayuni is in.
There's a guy who says his name is Gino.
Gino!
Yunopi, you don't play guitar? You want to play bass? You're saying that...
I usually laminate once. I'm sure they'll come flying in.
Chewie, you hit it with a "boom" and then a "wham"! And then, "kaboom".
That was a total no-no.
What's that? I'm going to play it quietly. Like a money car.
A xylophone.
Xylophones are rare in bands.
You mean percussion? Xylophone?
Thank you for watching!
I have an acoustic guitar at home.
You don't have anything?
I do, but you know how the C chord is usually the first chord in a beginner's chord chart?
I'm sure you'll find it.
I know.
I want you to sympathize with me.
But I couldn't even get that chord.
I've given up.
You think it'll be okay?
But it's a big house.
Didn't you say you had some kind of kokuna?
Yeah, my dad gave it to me.
I have a Lumirator guitar that my dad gave me.
I don't play it.
I'm going to play drums.
I'll start a band with the younger members.
What do you say? I'll be the drummer.
You're a keyboardist somehow.
I can play piano.
Emma sing? Vocals?
Why not Yuna?
Yuna.
I don't know. I think Emma can play guitar.
I can't imagine Ryutan playing the guitar.
But it's cool, right?
Yeah, it's cool.
Tsuda-san.
A little bit.
Hey!
Hey, you!
If we're going to form a band...
A band?
We talked about what we'd do.
Cocona wants to play drums.
I'm sure she'll get hit by a bee.
That's dangerous.
If it's dangerous, we'll play xylophone.
Xylophone still is.
Xylophone's a pom-pom.
What the hell?
Oh no, I can't go.
7th is the keyboard
Oh, stable
Xylophone wants to play bass.
Oh, you think you can do it?
Yeah, I don't know.
Two? I've been thinking.
Why?
What are you doing?
Ha-ha-ha.
How many piercings does Cocona have open? I don't know.
Six.
Oh.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's for sure!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
How do you feel?
Two.
I'm doing it today.
He says drama is all about stamina.
Physical?
Yeah.
Well, it's not about physical fitness.
I guess it's me.
I laugh.
But you know what?
In a band?
Bass guitar.
Keyboards.
Guitar, drums, vocals, and the vocalist is the guitar or that, the bass guitar.
I'm also a vocalist.
Yuno, if you were going to get pierced, where would you want to get it pierced?
I want a lower piercing.
My Yuno would get it in the bottom.
I want to sleep.
I don't mind if it hurts.
I want to get it pierced. I'm sure I'll get lots of piercings someday.
You know what I mean? I know.
You're short and blonde, and you're getting piercings all over the place.
But... my housemates probably don't like it when I have a lot of piercings.
Is that so?
I told you to stop.
I know, I know.
So I don't plan on getting them while I'm still a teenager.
You have another one?
No, there isn't.
I don't have one. I'm not going to open it while I'm still a teenager.
I'm not a blonde... but I want to be a blonde, too.
I want to have blonde hair, too.
I want to have blonde hair, I want to have blonde hair, I want to have blonde hair...
I was in the dry sun.
Was it?
Long time.
I'm a one-person person.
You could eat a little more, couldn't you? Here.
Can I have some more?
Yes, with white...
Three hundred thousand yen.
I want blonde hair. I want that.
I want to do blonde hair. I want to do that.
No, he won't get mad.
Watch out!
Did you have another one that was about the size of your face?
No, I don't think so.
No, his face was bigger.
Yeah, well, that's what you get with a guy like that.
That's scary.
This one's really salty.
It's delicious.
Yes, yes, yes... light.
I want it light.
So many things.
You said so.
No, I don't.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Come with me.
Today's lunch is
Carrot shiri-shiri-shiri-shi
At midnight last night
I made it after seeing yesterday's for the day
I was satisfied after seeing the day's worth.
I knew it.
I felt like I should eat with success
And then I thought, "I'll make it.
What time is it?
I started peeling carrots at 12:30
I started peeling carrots with a peeler.
I'm not going to tell you who my guesses are, because it's probably better if I don't.
I don't say who my guesses are, because I think it's probably better not to say.
I think I understand, yuno guessers. I think I can tell when I see them.
I don't know if you guys are watching.
Did you do the Ebituno email?
Yesterday, you know, the shrimp riddle that was posted on the official X?
I haven't done it yet.
I like Apeezy too.
But I still couldn't pick one pick.
So I voted for one in the referendum, and I voted for two in the other demi app.
I can't pick one, I can't pick one, I can't pick one, I can't pick one.
I can't do that. I want everyone to make their debut. If you spoil it, I'll be very angry.
What about the choreography you couldn't remember?
Did you try the B Club?
No.
Yeah, there's a blonde.
She's cute.
I could write.
I've always liked Korean groups, but I liked Twice when I was in the fourth grade.
Same thing.
I liked them.
Around eighth grade.
The summer after my freshman year.
I got into Bish and Buck.
And then I started watching a lot of Japanese idols.
That's how I started.
I started watching a lot of Japanese idols.
Did you try to play "Bikkurapon"?
I did.
It didn't work.
Oh, well...
What are you most likely to drink tomorrow, Yuuchan?
Fashion tea or Earl Grey tea latte.
Something fashionable.
I bought a Switch, so what games do you recommend?
I recommend the game I've been playing recently, Mario's Wonder, and that one.
And that one.
I can also play Apex, so Apex and...
Sprite, Supra.
How many plates of sushi do you usually have? Not more than 10? You'll be full from the other menu?
You mean a side menu? Yeah, a side menu.
Are you shooting an Emo Campy commercial today? No, sir. Yes, sir.
I'm an ambassador for Emocampy.
What's the feed?
I don't know.
I might.
Tell me what gummies you're into these days.
Don't tell anyone.
Why?
Tell me.
Who do you like?
Well...
I like momonga.
I don't know. I can't decide... but I have 80% of them in my bag.
I wonder.
Hmm.
Show me where you removed the mole.
I don't mind, but...
I won't show you, but you probably can't see it.
What's today's lipstick?
Here's today's lipstick.
Can you read?
Can you read it?
It's like DD Pyret.
Tell me the answer to the maze.
I don't want to.
And even if you know the answer, please don't tell anyone.
What do you put on a fried egg? First, put an egg in oil and fry it.
When the eggs are cooked, add a little water and close the lid.
Then, depending on your mood, you can put a little bit of water and close the lid.
When it's done, open the lid, scoop it out, put it on the table, and eat the white part around it.
Then you make a hole and pour just a couple of drops of soy sauce through it.
I put mascara on my lower eyelashes. I put mascara on my lower eyelashes.
I'm putting mascara on my lower eyelashes. I was going to say it's true, but I couldn't figure it out.
I'm just applying a little bit.
I put a little bit on.
And I'm drawing lines here, too.
Could it be anything but the source?
No, I don't know about that.
I like salt and pepper. I know.
I like salt and pepper.
But I don't like a lot of it, so I just put a little bit.
Strain the eggs through a tea strainer.
You see the yolk?
Do you do it in the pineapple?
No, I don't.
No, you don't?
No, I don't. I'd like to.
I'd like to, but...
Maybe when I'm shooting for a magazine or something.
I don't want to raise it too high.
It seems like makeup artists often do that.
They don't raise it too much.
I don't want to. I want to.
I wonder.
I wonder... Where did you get that dress?
I don't know. I'm wearing something I found.
Ayumi's here.
She's really cute.
That's right.
I knew I wanted it after the show.
I went to buy it right after the show.
The length of the string of the hoodie is too long.
What?
The lengths of the strings are all the same.
It bothers me.
I didn't do it consciously.
Wow!
I wonder how long I've been doing this for.
Can't you see how many minutes we've been doing this?
I can't.
We've been at it for 25 minutes.
Oh, yeah?
I see it.
Oh, zasad.
This much hair.
Okay, 15:20.
If it's 18 or 20, I'll stop. Okay, 19. 19.
I'll stop at 19.
I'll stop at 20.
I'm hungry.
Hmm? What does it say?
Way to go.
What I don't like about it is that it doesn't look too different when you do that filter.
I don't get it.
It doesn't make any sense.
That's funny.
That's great.
You two aren't going?
One more.
Cold contamination.
That's right.
Zaser school is next in seven.
Me.
стало nam
l in declined
LOL
présent
air
I'll put it in your ear.
It's the worst thing I've ever heard.
I said the words you're about to say.
I'm not going to say it.
I knew it! I knew it! It's all puckered up here!
Right here.
It looks pokey.
It looks poked.
So thin.
Wow, just like me.
What?
Are you looking at me?
Can you tell we have the same comb?
That part, too?
Lawson.
Awww.
We're all in this together, Lawson.
But I tried all kinds of convenience stores.
Like New Days in Tokyo.
I bought a lot of things at a lot of places.
Here you go.
This is the best.
Lawson is the best.
Yes, it's the best
The first one is the thinnest.
That's right.
You really did your research.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
But it's broken. It's coming off right here. Oh.
You're graduating from Lawson.
I'll buy that comb. It's a Bose, but I think it's good.
You should get your eyebrows trimmed. I think that's a good idea.
It might come in handy in the future. Bye-bye.